ILR School Associate Dean's Office Jon Levy Additional Files /4200
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
ILR School Associate Dean's Office Jon Levy Additional Files
1987- 1995
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
New State School of Industrial and Labor Relations (NYSSILR)
Levy, John
/4200
1.5 cubic feet
1.5 linear ft.
Records (documents), case files.
8051239
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, July 01, 2014
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, October 04, 2016
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Levy, Jon; New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations; New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations. Associate Dean's Office
8051239
- Expenses NCW, 1994-1995 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- NCW Reponses, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- NCW Congressional Briefing 11/15/94, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Lists NCW Dialogue + Dinner INU., 1994 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- NCW email 11/15-16/94, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Assent NCW, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Nov. Survey CW List, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Ret'd NCW Survey, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- NCW, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- NCW 4/10-12, 1994-1995 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Correspondence NCW 6/93, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- NCW Cornell Consortium (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Cornell Proposal NCW 8/27/93, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Comparisons DOL RFP and Public Law (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Public Law creating NCW, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- DOL Request for Proposals NCW, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- National Center for the Workplace, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- DC History Nat CTR, 1987-1991 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- D.C., 1991 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Cornell Proposal NCW 5/10/93, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Building Program Information, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- 6/17/94 Phase 1+2 Placements, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Eastman Cases Projects Renovations, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Equip Lists, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- PAR /SFC 6/21/93 Renov., 1993 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Building Program Drafts, 1992-1993 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- New Bldg., 1994 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- Architect - Special Finishes - Bldg. 95, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 28)
- Blakeney Report 11/6/89, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 29)
- ILR Master Plan Project, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- School Facilities (A), 1990-1991 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- School Facilities (B), 1988-1990 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Classroom Technology Planning, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Extra Copies Related to Planning New Facilities, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Finances 1995 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- JDL Travel Reinb 1/1/95, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 6)